Further, ICICI Lomd is going to announce its
results today after the market closes
but Varun is already ready with his estimate.
Varun ji, if you tell me, then the results will be
on the lower side, that is, they will be
on the weaker side. The net premium of this company will
increase by around 2% from ₹3836
crore to ₹3905 crore. There will be a decline in the profit after a
cut of ₹590 crore and
it will come to around ₹368 crore. The gross
direct premium income will
increase by around 20% in 10 years.
You will see a slight impact in the net premium and whatever is there, due to which the
overall net premium will
decline somewhere and due to that the profit will also
decline. The combined ratio will
remain around 102. An increase in the operating cost is being
estimated.
Investment will also be
seen falling sequentially, the
impact of which you will see in the profits. The
claim ratio is going to decrease slightly.
Expensive will also be a little less, the net commission
ratio which is 3.9% will come, the combination is
less than 102, 105, it
is estimated to come around 102, so
if you look at the ratios, there is a little bit of mix,
but if you look at the top line and bottom line, there will be
a hit, and especially the
profit is going to fall by around 37%,
so this is the
result estimate for you, ICICI Lohm, meaning there wo
n't be much volatility, then
why are the stocks running, it will
not be downloaded from mobile, it will be downloaded in JP like this,
what will happen by taking such reports,
all the updates have been done, today also, tomorrow the
reports are coming, everyone wants to
buy an insurance company, because what happens,
when it is a matter, it seems like a feast,
then everyone remembers the 10, 15, 20 year investment
and then see, okay, if it is a 10, 20
year, let's buy ICICI, let's buy SBI
Life,
such people have also started saying that
most of the downloads
[laughs], this
is the strength of LIC, why, I said right,
this is the strength of LIC  And Anil ji, this
downgrade upgrade Anil ji should be done blindly, right
now the company which had
taken down great yesterday, no need today
and it itself is saying that it is not known
when it will go, right now it is in heavy losses, so after a
little careful consideration, the credentials of the person who is downgrading or
upgrading should also be
checked once,
very good, Bansal ji and Kunal ji are
giving their LIC very strongly for continuous investment,
from here the big elephant will move slowly, do
not expect it to run away, it is exactly its wish.